Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Flyers, 1977-1985
  - Soul Power '77 at Junior High School 123, 1977-10-14; Black Willie; Winston; Red; Lil Monk; Zulu Queens (Volume 1)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambo, Mighty Zulu Nation, Mr. Biggs, Queen Kenya
  - The Last of the Summer Block Party's Tours for D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and his Zulu Nation at Bronx River Projects, Castle Hill Projects, 1977-08-10-1977-08-17 (Volume 1)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zulu Nation
  - Uptown Meets Downtown Part 2 at Webster P.A.L., 1978-03-17; Bambaataa, Afrika (Volume 1)
    D.J. Afrika Islam & Ed-LaRock & the Mayberry Crew vs. D.J. Breakout & Baron
  - Futuristic Funk Freak Disco at Junior High School 123; Freak on Out '77 at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1977-12-09-1977-12-10; D.J. Sinbad; Tippy Tip; Neffertiti Rock; Zulu Nation (Volume 1)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambo, D.J. Afrika Queen Kenya, Mr. Biggs, Mighty Zulu Nation
  - A Funky Bootzilla Sureshot at Bronx River Center, 1978-04-08; Zulu Nation; C.C. Crew (Volume 1)
  - Uptown Freak Boogie! At The Spot; Downtown Freak Boogie at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1978-01-20-1978-01-21 (Volume 1)
    D.J. Afrika Islam, Ed-La-Rock, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambo, Mr. Bigs, Zulu Queens
  - Downtown Freak Boogie at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1978-01-21; Home of God Productions (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu, Mr. Biggs, the Zulu Queens.
  - A Music Tribute to the Godfather of Soul James Brown at Bronx River Projects Center, 1976-11-12; The Organization (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and his Zulu Nation.
  - Shakara '77 at Junior High School 123, 1977-10-07; The Organization (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambo, and the Zulu Nation.
  - Shakara Freak Funkathon 78 at Junior High School 123, 1978-03-03 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambu, the Zulu Nation, Mr. Biggs, and Lil Akbar.
  - D.J. Mario and His Chuck Chuck City Crew at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1978-04-07-1978-04-08 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and D.J. Mario.
  - First Jam Boogie at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1976-12-10; Division for Youth (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa.
  - Last Chance Christmas Freak Out at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1977-12-23 (Volume 2)
  - D.J. Afrika Bambaataa Top 15 Records of February, 1977-02; Bronx River Neighborhood Centers, Inc. (Volume 2)
    On Bronx River Neighborhood Center letterhead.
  - A Soul Knockout Jamming Disco at James Monroe High School, 1978-10-13 (Volume 2)
    Disco King Mario, D.J. Nicky Dee, D.J. Ronnie Ron, D.J. Afrika Islam, D.J. Afrika Amad, D.J. Desi Des, D.J. Sinbad, D.J. Afrika Zambu, and the Chuck City Crew.
  - A Disco Throw Down at Bronx River Center, 1978-03-24; Bambaataa, Afrika; Zambu (Volume 2)
    Disco King Mario and Starsky vs. D.J. Kojak
  - The Battle of the Dee Jays at Bronx River Center, 1978-04-14; Bambaataa, Afrika; Leaa (Volume 2)
  - Another Sure Shot Disco at Junior High School 123, 1978-04-22; Disco King Mario; Bambaataa, Afrika; C.C Crews; Zula Nation (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and Zulu Nation, D.J. Frog and the Toad Nation.
  - Four shows at Bronx River Community Center, Ronnie's Disco Inferno, and I.S. 167, 1978-04-15-1978-05-06 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and his Zulu Nation, D.J. Afrika Zambo and the Zulu Kings.
  - Sunday Rock with the Rockers at Ronnie's Disco Inferno, 1977-04-03 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and his Zulu Nation, D.J. Afrika Zambo, Queen Kenya, Mr. Big, and the Western Man Mr. Cowboy.
  - Soul Sonic Freakin Hell at The Spot, 1978-01-06 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Islam and D.J. Ed La Rock.
  - Baby Come Back at Bronx River Center, 1978-02-11 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zulu Nation Organization, Zulu Queens, and Mr. Biggs.
  - This Is A Shirley Audrey Jill Vanessa Lisa FFC. at Bronx River Center, 1978-02-24 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Shirley, Lisa, Audrey, Jill, and Vanessa.
  - Disco King Mario on ABC Television at Bronx River Community Center, 1978-01-26 (Volume 2)
    Disco King Mario, C.C. Crew, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, and Zulu Nation.
  - Another Sureshot Disco at Junior High School 123, 1978-12-02 (Volume 2)
    Disco King Mario and the Chuck City Crew, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zulu Nation, Mr. Biggs, D.J. Nicky Dee, D.J. Ronnie Ron, MC Starsky, D.J. Desi Des, and D.J. Kenny Ken.
  - Soulsonic Weekend Boogie at Bronx River Neighborhood, 1978-02-18-1978-02-25 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and Ahad and the Mighty Zulu Nation, Casanova Fly.
  - Soulsonic Freak Boogie at Webster P.A.L., 1978-02-25 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Casanova Fly vs D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and Zambu and the Mighty Zulu Nation along with Mr. Biggs and the Zulu Queens.
  - Super Jam Funk Boogie at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1978-03-11; Bambaataa, Afrika; Zambu (Volume 2)
  - Rock Steady at The Spot, 1978-02-18 (Volume 2)
  - Pre Easter Disco for Young Adults at Whitney Young Center, 1978-03-25; Bee Bop; Ray Ray (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and Zambu, Mr. Biggs, and Lil Akbar.
  - The Battle of the Dee Jays at Junior High School 123, 1978-12-16; Sudanese Productions; LEAA (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Islam and Kool D.J. OZ vs D.J. Afrika PT LaRock and Tony Tee vs D.J. Isaac, D.J. Afrika Khayan, and D.J. Squirpy LaRock.
  - Spank Disco at Bronx River Community Center, 1978-12-22 (Volume 2)
  - New Year's Eve Jam Boogie at Bronx River Community Center, 1978-12-31 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Disco King Mario, and the Chuck City Crew.
  - Christmas shows at T-Connection and Club Monte Rey, 1978-12-25-1978-12-27; Jazzy Dee Productions (Volume 2)
    The Brothers Disco, D.J. Breakout, D.J. Baron, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, and Death Partners Disco.
  - Grand Funk Shake Ya Rump Disco at Bronx Neighborhood Center, 1979-01-12 (Volume 2)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu and Jazzy Jay, D.J. Sinbad, MCs Mr. Biggs, Ice Ice, Lisa Lee, Hutch Hutch, Cholly Rock, Sun Dance, and Pow Wow.
  - The Music Company, 1979 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Cheri "Murphy's Law", Chas Jankel "Questionaire", Rita Marley "One Draw", Eloise Whitaker "Don't Turn Your Back on Love", Joy "I Need Your Love"
    51
  - Battle-79 at Remington-Boys Club, 1980; R. Levister Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    C.B. Crew, Super Dynamite '3', Love Squigg, Turtle Dove, Rob the Gold, Devastating "4", Malibu-Rob-Ski, Tricky-Tee, Harry-O, Collins Brothers
    196
    New Rochelle, New York
  - New Years Eve Enjoy 12 Hours of Contenious Dancing 8PM Till 8AM at the Roller World, 1980 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Grasshopper, Taphy, Redd, Winnie Win & Just 4, Broadcast, Jazzy J., Red Alert, Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy 5
    24
  - Nubian and Stonecity Prod. Presents "A Youth Night Super Jam" at the Blue Room, 1981; Nubian Productions; Stonecity Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy-Jay, Red Alert, Soulsonic Force
    183
  - An Elvis Down Punk Rock Jam Disco at Bronx River Community Center, 1981; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soulsonic Force
    192
  - Soulsonic Freakjam at 85 Riverdale Ave., 1977-01-06; Organization Yonkers (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambo, D.J. Mr. Biggs, D.J. Afrika Queen Kenya
    148
  - Friday Feb. 18 at Bond International Casino, 1977-02-18-1983-02-20 (Box 547, Folder C)
    One Last Shot, C-Bank, D.J. The Perfect Beat, Afrika Bambaata, Michael Jackson, Breaking Bells, Crash Crew
    123
  - Live and Disco at Roseland, 1977-04-02-1983-04-16 (Box 547, Folder C)
    "Candy Girl", D.J. Chuck Leonard Birthday, Soul Sonic Force, Visual
    116
  - D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and Zambo along with D.J. Cowboy, Mr. Biggs and Queen Kenya at Junior High School 123, 1977-05-27-1983-05-27; Zulu Nation (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambo, D.J. Cowboy, Mr. Biggs, Queen Kenya
    101
  - The Last of the Block Partys for D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and his Zulu Nation at Bronx River Projects, Castle Hill Projects, 1977-08-10-1977-08-17 (Box 547, Folder C)
    104
  - The Last of the Summer Block Partys at Bronx River Projects, Castle Hill Projects Big Park, Bronx River Projects, 1977-08-10-1977-08-17 (Box 547, Folder C)
    125
  - Soulsonic Groove Ya'll-Say What-Say Wee-Oo at Bronx River Projects Old Center, 1977-08-30 (Box 547, Folder C)
    117
  - Yonkers Soulsonic Jam at Riverview Towers Projects, 1977-09-02 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa & his Zulu Nation
    158
  - Freak Out '77 at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1977-12-10; Tippy Tip; Neffertiti Rock (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa & Mighty Zulu Nation
    103
  - The Battle of the Zulu Brothers at Junior High School 123, 1977-12-28 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Zambo & Amad vs. D.J. Afrika Islam & Ed La Rock, The Mighty Zulu Nation
    173
  - We Will Rock You at The "Spot", 1978-01-06 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Islam, D.J. Ed. La. Rock, Mayberry Crew
    159
  - A Disco Dance at Evander, 1978-01-27; Brothers Disco, The (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Breakout, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and his Zulu Nation, D.J. Baron and the Breakout Crew
    112
  - The Chuck City Crew Presents the Serious Battle Jointski at J.H.S. 123, 1978-03-31 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Disco King Mario & Nicky Dee and the Voice of Starsky vs. D.J. Afrika Bambaataa & Zambu with the Voice of Mr. Biggs
    95
  - Jam Rocker Dub Disco at Bronx River Center, 1978-04-15; Zulu Nation (Box 547, Folder C)
    180
  - Second Annual Freak-A-Thon at the Super Plush Tracey Towers, 1978-04-29; Foxy Lady (Box 547, Folder C)
    Africa Bambaataa & His Zulu Nation, D.J. Prince of Funk & AL "G"
    97
  - Super Rock-A-Tron at James Monroe H.S., 1978-05-14 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu & Jazzy Jay, D.J. Sinbad, Soulsonic M.C.s
    121
  - Funk Attack '78 at Junior High School 131, 1978-06-10; D.J. Sinbad (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa & Zambu with the Voice of Mr. Biggs, D.J. Afrika Lil Khayan & Squippy LA Rock with D.J. Curtis-SCOH & Richie Rich
    110
  - Zulu Funk Block Party at Bronx River Center, Junior High School 123, 1978-07-21-1978-07-22 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Breakout & Barron, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and his Mighty Zulu Nation
    109
  - 3rd Annual Disco Tribute to Sly Stone at Bronx River Community Center, 1978-11-10; Zulu Nation (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambo & M.C. Mr. Biggs
    208
  - A Sure Shot Boogie at I.S. 167, 1978-12-23; Sudanese Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu & Sinbad, D.J. Jazzy-Jay, M.C. Mr. Biggs, Cholly-Rock, Sundance, Ice-Ice, Lambu, Pow-Wow, Lisa-Lee, Brothers Disco
    130
  - An Old Time .50-$1.00 Disco Jam at Bronx River Community Center, 1979-01-24-1979-01-26; Nubian Productions; Small Fry Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu & Jazzy Jay, D.J. Sinbad, MC.'s Mr. Biggs, Lisa Lee, Ice Ice, Pow-Wow, Hutch Hutch, Sundance, Cholly Rock, D.J. Afrika Islam, Grand Wizzard Theodore & D.J. Superman, M.C. Busy Bug Starski & Ell J.
    108
  - Sureshot the Body Rock Disco at Club Mandingo, 1979-02-03 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Kool D.J. Herc
    190
    Mt. Vernon, New York
  - Jungle Rock City at Bronx River Comm. Center, 1979-02-10 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Bambaataa, Kool D.J. A.J.
    165
  - Kool D.J. AJ's 1st Anniversary at Mitchell Gym, 1979-03-09 (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Star-Ski, Pete D.J. Jones, Theodore
    40
  - A Night of Disco Madness at I.S. 195, 1979-03-10; Nubian Productions; Fantasy Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Sinbad, Mr. Biggs, Hutch Hutch, Lisa Lee, MC's Pow Wow, Ice Ice, Sundance, Lambu, The Mighty Zulu Nation, D.J. Donald D
    30
    Harlem, New York
  - Ladies Nite Disco at Bronx River Comm. Center, 1979-04-27; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu & Jazzy Jay, D.J. Sinbad, Soulsonic Force MC's
    163
  - Soulsonic to the Rock Disco at Rodbenders Club, 1979-05-11; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Grand Kid Jazzy Jay, Mr. Biggs
    38
  - A Funky Friday at Southfield Village Community Center, 1979-05-18; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    Soulsonic Funk Sounds, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu, Jazzy Jay, D.J. Sinbad, D.J. Afrika Islam
    48
    Stamford, Connecticut
  - Portchester's Fly Girl Disco Weekend at Carpenters Hall, 1979-06-02-1979-06-15 (Box 547, Folder A)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu, The Grand Kid Jazzy Jay, and Soulsonic Force MCs.
    Also includes listings for the Westchester Senior Day Dance and the Connecticut US Senior Day Dance.
    1
    Portchester, New York
  - A Zulu Nation Turnout at Clinton Proj Theater Art's Center, 1979-06-06; Zulu Nation (Box 547, Folder B)
    Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Jazzy 3 MC's, The Master Reid, Sun Dance, Easy 'Dee, D.J. Solid Gold, D.J. Speedy, Terry 'T'
    16
  - Weschester's Senior Day Disco Dance at the Polish Community Center, 1979-06-08; Nubian Productions; Yonkers Zulu Nation (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Zambu & D.J. Sinbad, Soulsonic Force M.C.'s
    50
  - Nubian & Yonkers Zulunation Production Presents Polish Community Center, 1979-06-08; Nubian Productions; Yonkers Zulu Nation (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu & Jazzy Jay, D.J. Sinbad, Soul Sonic force MC's
    111
  - Disco Madness, Sciencefiction Funk at the Yerwood Community Center, 1979-06-15; Nubian Productions; C.B. Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Zambu, D.J. Jazzy Jay, The C.B. Crew, The Soulsonic Force MC's
    118
  - Cosmic Funk Patty Duke Freak Dance at Theater Arts Center, 1979-06-16; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zambu, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Soulsonic Force MC's
    119
  - Block Party Tribute to The Man Who Started it All., The True Godfather of the B-Beats at Bronx River Center, 1979-07-13; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Zumbu & Jazzy Jay, Soulsonic Force M.C.'s
    49
  - A Shureshot Throwdown featuring Theodore at 149st & Bruckner Blvd, 1979-08-12; Disco King Mario; Jimmy and the Big Mac Crew (Box 547, Folder B)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Zulu Nation, Breakout, Baron, Kool D.J. A.J., Kool Herc, Kool D.J. Dee, Grandmaster Flash, D.J. Islam
    31
  - Nubian & Bronx River Center Production Presents Youth Core Day Disco at Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1979-08-24; Nubian Productions; Bronx River Community Center (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Afrika Islam, D.J. Afrika Isaac, Soulsonic Force M.C.'s, Mr. Biggs, Hutch Hutch, Pow-Wow, Lisa Lee, Ice Ice, Sundance
    27
  - The 1979 Up-Coming D.J.s Convention!! At the P.A.L., 1979-08-24; P.A.L. Teen Council; Jazzy Dee Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Touch of Class Disco, Untouchable Crew, The Players, D.J. Breakout, D.J. Baron, Theodore, Bambaataa, Charlie Chase, P.T. Disco Crew, T.N.T. Disco, Sureshots Brothers
    198
  - Herculord's, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Charlie Chase, 1979-09-07; P.A.L. Teen Council; P.A.L. Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    Herculord's Kool Herc, D.J. Clark Kent, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and the Zulu Nation & D.J. Islam and the funkmachine, D.J. Charlie Chase and The Chase Crew, busybee Starski
    41
  - Back to school! Patty Duke Punk Rock Disco, 1979-10-05; Nubian Productions; Monroe High School Baseball (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Soulsonic Force M.C.'s, Mr. Biggs, Hutch Hutch, Pow Wow, Lisa Lee, Sundance, Ice Ice, The Mighty Zulu Nation
    35
  - 4th Zulu Nation Anniversary Tribute for James Brown & Sly and the Family Stone at Bronx River Community Center, 1979-11-10; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Soulsonic Force M.C.'s, D.J. Afrika Islam & D.J. Afrika Issac
    106
  - 4th Annual Tribute to James Brown at Bronx River Center, 1979-11-10; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Soulsonic Force MC's, the Mighty Zulu Nation
    154
  - A Disco Tribute to Sly Stone at Bronx River Community Center, 1979-11-10; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    155
  - Announcing Super Disco Affair at Yerwood Center, 1979-11-16 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Terrible "T"-N-Company, The T-Force MC's
    138
  - Sureshot the Bodyrock Disco Pt. 3 at T-Connection, 1979-11-24; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Soulsonic Force M.C.'s, Kool D.J. Herc, Clark Kent, J.C.
    201
  - Bodyrockin' the P.A.L., 1979-11-30; Riley, Anthony; P.A.L. Productions (Box 547, Folder A)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, the Kool D.J. AJ Show, and FunBox.
    4
  - Sure Shot Volume One Number Three clipping, 1979-12-06 (Box 547, Folder C)
    207
  - Dance-A-Thon Disco Pt. 1 at Bronx River Center, 1979-12-14; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    Tex D.J. Hollywood & Crew, Kool D.J. Dee, Tyrone the Mixologist, Feva Dee & Al Gee
    44
  - 2nd Annual D.J. Convention, 1979-12-15; P.A.L. Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    Touch of Class, Mean machine crew, M&M crew, Sure Shot Brothers, Heavenly 7 crew, Kid Cisco Rock
    33
  - A Disco Jam Sureshot at Cardinal Hayes H.S., 1979-12-22; Cardinal Hayes High School (Box 547, Folder B)
    Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Master-B, Sundance, Master-Ice, Lisa-Lee, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Afrika Islam
    47
  - "The Last of the Year" Funk Jam Tour at Ecstasy Garage Disco, T-Connection, and Bronx River Center, 1979-12-26-1979-12-31; Esquire, Buddy; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder A)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, and the Soulsonic Force MCs.
    5
  - Alton D. Chase City-Wide Rapper's Contest at the Savoy Manor (program schedule), 1979-12-28 (Box 547, Folder A)
    D.J. AJ, Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Grandmaster Casanova Fly, Grandmaster Flash, as well as 23 other groups and soloists.
    2
  - New Years Eve Funk Jam Boogie at Bronx River Center, 1979-12-31; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Hutch-Hutch, Pow-Wow, Ice-Ice, Lisa-Lee, Sundance, Master-Ice, Master-B
    43
  - A New Years Eve Funk Jamboogie 79-80's at Bronx River Center, 1979-12-31; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay
    189
  - New Years Eve Funk Jam Boogie at Bronx River Center, 1979-12-31; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Afrika Islam & Isaac, The Mighty Zulu Nation
    200
  - Dance-A-Thon Disco Pt. 2 at Audobon Ballroom, 1980-01-11; Esquire, Buddy; Nubian Productions; R. Livister; S.U.R.E. Productions (Box 547, Folder A)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, C.B. Crew, The Funk Machine, The Kool D.J. AJ Show, and Dynamite Brothers.
    9
  - Dance-A-Thon Disco Pt. 2 at Audobon Ballroom, 1980-01-11; Nubian Productions; R. Livister; S.U.R.E. Productions (Box 547, Folder A)
    Alternate version.
    10
  - Afrika Bambaataa at Monroe High School, 1980-01-12; Nubian Productions; Jazzy Dee Productions (Box 547, Folder A)
    The Brothers Disco, Breakout, Baron, the Funky 4, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, and the Soulsonic Force MCs.
    6
  - The Long Awaited Jam Disco at Bronx River Center, 1980-01-18; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder A)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Grandmaster Flash, and others.
    7
  - The Coming of the Age of Zulu Funk at Ecstasy Garage Disco, 1980-01-25; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Soulsonic Force MC's
    191
  - A Punk Rock Elvis Weekend Disco at Bronx River Center and T-Connection, 1980-02-01-1980-02-02; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Mr. Biggs, Pow Wow, Hutch Hutch, Lisa Lee, Sundance, Ice Ice, Master Ice, Master B
    167
  - Nubian & JazzyDee Productions presents Funkin for the funk Disco at Bronx River Center, 1980-02-10; Nubian Productions; Jazzy Dee Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Brothers Disco, Jazzy Jay, Soul Sonic Force MCs
    174
  - A Funkadelic Experience at Ecstasy Garage Disco, 1980-02-15; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force
    194
  - Two Big Days T Connection presents 1st Annual D.J. & MC Contest, 1980-02-16-1980-02-17 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Starsky, AJ, Sinbad, Flash, Charlie Chase, Clark Kent, Theodore, Breakout, Bambaataa, Baron, Furious 5, Mercedies Ladies, Funky Four, Spooning Gee, L Bros., Frankie Roll, Herculords, Bambaataa Crew, Inter City Crew, Kool Kyle
    37
  - The Grand Musicians at The Paradise of the Bronx, 1980-02-22 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Ricky Dee, Chino-Rockwell, Fearless Fred, Junie Salsa, Mello Rock, Gueli Guel, Kid Scorpio, Kid Faze, African Bambaataa, Soul Sonic Force, Grand Disco Wizard, Saint Peters
    34
  - An Elvis Down Punk Rock Jam Disco at Bronx River Community Center, 1980-02-22; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force, Herc Clark Kent, Mean Machine
    205
  - A Connecticut Zulu Nation Turnoutdisco at Southfield Village Community Center, 1980-02-23; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    175
  - A Connecticut Zulu Nation Turnoutdisco at Southfield Village Community Center, 1980-02-23; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    209
  - The First Disco "Rose Awards" Show at Ecstasy Garage Disco, 1980-03-01 (Box 547, Folder A)
    11
  - A Connecticut Punk Rock Throwdown at Yerwood Center, 1980-03-07; Nubian Productions; TT Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force, Terrible T, Static Control
    32
  - Jungle Rock City at The T-Connection, 1980-03-15; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy-Jay, Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.'s, Funky 4 plus 1
    188
  - A Rhythm & Funk JamDisco at Staten Island Comm. Corp., 1980-03-29; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s, The Mighty Zulu Nation
    172
    Staten Island, New York
  - A Super Star Jam Session"at Ecstasy Garage Disco, 1980-04-01 (Box 547, Folder C)
    The Kool D.J. A.J. Show, Starky, Theodore, The Fantastic 5 M.C.s, Afrika Bambaataa, Soulsonic Force M.C.s, Cold Crush Brothers, Charlie Chase, Tony-Tone, KoolDee
    142
  - An Easter Night Funk Jam Disco at Bronx River Center, 1980-04-06; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.'s, D.J. E-Z E., M.C. Shawnski, D.J. Banana Joe, M.C. Vinnie V.
    164
  - A Disco Tribute to Parliament Funkadelic at James Monroe High School, 1980-04-11; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.'s, Grand Wizard Theodore, Fantastic 5 M.C.'s
    195
  - A Disco Tribute to all the Crews at The T-Connection Disco, 1980-04-18; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s
    171
  - A Double Birthday Celebration for HERC and BAMBAATAA at The T Connection, 1980-04-19 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Bambaataa, Kurtis Blow, Herculord's, Clark Kent, JayCee, The Grand Wizard Theodore, Kool Kyle, Starchild, Disco Dolls
    15
  - Bronx Citywide H.S. Super Show at Webster PAL, 1980-04-26 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Grand Master Flash, Furious 5, Funky 4+1, Kool D.J. AJ, Busy-Bee, E-Man, Theodore
    46
  - Sounds of the City at The Royal Villa Play House, 1980-04-26; Phoenix Drill Team Productions (Box 547, Folder C)